Guide to the Cornell University Board of Trustees records, 1865-2001.
Cornell University Board of Trustees records, 1865-2001
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University Board of Trustees records, 1865-2001
2-3-74
Cornell University. Board of Trustees.
96.4 cubic ft.; 14.4 cubic ft.
Minutes and work folders.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Minutes and work folders for Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meetings.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Minutes and work folders for Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meetings.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Cornell University--Administration.; Cornell University--Executive Committee--Board of Trustees.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to permission of office of origin.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Trustee Minutes and Work Folders
Series II. Folders of the Executive Committee and Board of Trustees
Series III. Photographs
RELATED MATERIALS
Includes collection #2-5-5.
For the published Proceedings of the Board of Trustees of Cornell University see Archives LD1341.A1.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Trustee Minutes and Work Folders
  (Note: Boxes 32-43 carry two numbers, as they were numbered 1-12 by the donor)
  - Oct. 17, 1865 - June 1872 (Box 77)
  - Oct. 1873 -June 1885 (Box 78)
  - Oct. 1886 - June 1898 (actually contains 1886-1892) (Box 79)
  - Oct. 1899 - June 1908 (actually contains 1893-1907) (Box 80)
  - Oct. 1909 - June 1911 (Box 81)
  - Oct. 1912 - June 1913 (Box 82)
  - Oct. 1914 - June 1916 (Box 83)
  - Oct. 1917 - 1920? (Box 84)
  - 1920-07-23-1921-12-17 (Box 1)
  - 1922-01-07-1923-09-22 (Box 2)
  - 1923-10-12-1925-06-13 (Box 3)
  - 1925-06-15-1927-06-18 (Box 4)
  - 1927-08-06-1929-06-17 (Box 5)
  - 1929-07-17-1930-10-24 (Box 6)
  - 1930-10-25-1931-12-2 (Box 7)
  - January 16, 1.932 - February 11, 1933 (Box 8)
  - 1933-03-17-1934-07-28 (Box 9)
  - 1934-09-08-1935-10-26 (Box 10)
  - 1935-11-01-1937-01-30 (Box 11)
  - 1937-02-18-1938-01-29 (Box 12)
  - 1938-02-10-1939-01-21 (Box 13)
  - 1939-02-04-1940-01-20 (Box 14)
  - 1940-02-29-1940-10-25 (Box 15)
  - 1940-11-07-1941-06-16 (Box 16)
  - 1941-08-12-1942-04-25 (Box 17)
  - 1942-05-23-1943-03-20 (Box 18)
  - 1943-05-01-1944-06-26 (Box 19)
  - 1944-09-09-1945-12-15 (Box 20)
  - 1946-01-18-1946-09-9 (Box 21)
  - 1946-10-09-1947-04-26 (Box 22)
  - 1947-05-17-1947-11-18 (Box 23)
  - 1947-12-16-1948-06-14 (Box 24)
  - 1948-07-24-1949-06-13 (Box 25)
  - 1949-08-06-1950-09-19 (Box 26)
  - 1950-10-20-1952-03-3 (Box 27)
  - 1952-04-25-1953-08-20 (Box 28)
  - 1953-10-15-1955-04-18 (Box 29)
  - 1955-06-12-1956-04-14 (Box 30)
  - 1956-05-15-1956-06-11 (Box 31)
  - Membership Committee folders, 1933-1964
  - 1956-08-1957-09 (Box 32)
  - October 1957- January 1959 (Box 33)
  - 1959-02-1960-04 (Box 34)
  - 1960-08-1960-12 (Box 35)
  - 1961-01-1961-09 (Box 36)
  - 1961-10-1962-06 (Box 37)
  - 1962-08-1963-04 (Box 38)
  - May, 1963 - February 1964 (Box 39)
  - 1964-03-1964-10 (Box 40)
  - November 1964 - June, 1965 (Box 41)
  - July, 1965 - February 1966 (Box 42)
  - March 1966 - June, 1966. (Box 43)
  - May, 1969 - October 17-18, 1969 (Box 44)
  - November 18, 1969-April 10-11,1970 (Box 45)
  - May 12, 1970-June, 1970 (Box 46)
  - 1966-10-1967-03 (Box 47)
  - 1967-04-1967-09 (Box 48)
  - 1967-10-1968-04 (Box 49)
  - 1968-05-1968-11 (Box 50)
  - 1968-12-1969-04 (Box 51)
  - June 6, 1971-January 20,1972 (May 1969-June 1970, see Boxes 44-46) (Box 52)
  - January 21-22, 1972-July 12, 1972 (Box 53)
  - 1972-09-20-1973-03-15 (Box 54)
  - 1970-07-21-1971-01-23 (Box 55)
  - 1971-02-16-1971-06-05 (Box 56)
- Series II. Work Folders of the Executive Committee and Board of Trustees
  - Board, March 16-17, 1973 (Box 57)
  - Executive Committee, 4/18/73 (Box 57)
  - Executive Committee, 5/23/73 (Box 57)
  - Board, 5/24/73 (Box 57)
  - Executive Committee, 7/19/73 (Box 57)
  - Executive Committee, 9/11/73 (Box 57)
  - Executive Committee, 10/18/73 (Box 57)
  - Board, October 19 - 20, 1973 (Box 57)
  - Executive Committee, 11/15/73 (Box 58)
  - Executive Committee, 12/11/73 (Box 58)
  - Executive Committee, 1/17/74 (Box 58)
  - Board, January 18-19, 1974 (Box 58)
  - Executive Committee, 2/12/74 (Box 58)
  - Executive Committee, 3/14/74 (Box 58)
  - Executive Committee, 4/17/74 (Box 58)
  - Executive Committee, 5/14/74 (Box 58)
  - Executive Committee, 6/1/74 (Box 58)
  - Board, 6/2/74 (Box 58)
  - Executive Committee, 7/18/74 (Box 59)
  - Executive Committee, 9/10/74 (Box 59)
  - Trustee Orientation, 10/2/74 (Box 59)
  - Executive Committee, 10/10/74 (Box 59)
  - Board, October 11-12, 1974 (Box 59)
  - Executive Committee, 11/12/74 (Box 59)
  - Executive Committee, 12/10/74 (Box 59)
  - Executive Committee, 1/16/75 (Box 59)
  - Board, January 17-18, 1975 (Box 59)
  - Executive Committee, 2/11/75 (Box 59)
  - Executive Committee, 3/13/75 (Box 59)
  - Board, March 14-15, 1975 (Box 60)
  - Executive Committee, 4/8/75 (Box 60)
  - Executive Committee, 5/14/75 (Box 60)
  - Executive Committee, 5/31/75 (Box 60)
  - Board, 6/1/75 (Box 60)
  - Executive Committee, 7/22/75 (Box 60)
  - Executive Committee, 9/9/75 (Box 60)
  - Executive Committee, 10/9/75 (Box 60)
  - Board, October 10-11, 1975 (Box 60)
  - Executive Committee, 11/11/75 (Box 60)
  - Executive Committee, 12/9/75 (Box 61)
  - Executive Committee, 1/29/76 (Box 61)
  - Board Executive Committee, January 30-31, 1976, March 18, 1976 (Box 61)
  - Board, March 19-20, 1976 (Box 61)
  - Executive Committee, 5/11/76 (Box 61)
  - EC, 5/26/76 (Box 61)
  - Board, 5/27/76 (Box 61)
  - Special Mtg./Executive Committee, 6/30/76 (Box 62)
  - Executive Committee, 7/28/76 (Box 62)
  - Executive Committee, 9/14/76 (Box 62)
  - Executive Committee, 10/21/76 (Box 62)
  - Board, October 22-23, 1976 (Box 62)
  - Executive Committee, 11/9/76 (Box 62)
  - Executive Committee, 12/14/76 (Box 62)
  - Executive Committee, 1/27/77 (Box 62)
  - Board, January 28-29, 1977 (Box 62)
  - Special. Mtg./Board, 2/16/77 (Box 63)
  - Executive Committee, 3/17/77 (Box 63)
  - Board, March 18-19, 1977 (Box 63)
  - Executive Committee, 4/12/77 (Box 63)
  - Executive Committee, 5/10/77 (Box 63)
  - Executive Committee, 5/28/77 (Box 63)
  - Board, 5/29/77 (Box 63)
  - Executive Committee, 7/19/77 (Box 63)
  - Executive Committee, September 7, 197? (Box 63)
  - Executive Committee, 10/6/77 (Box 63)
  - Board, October 7-8, 1977 (Box 64)
  - Executive Committee, 11/9/77 (Box 64)
  - Executive Committee, 12/13/77 (Box 64)
  - Executive Committee, 1/26/78 (Box 64)
  - Board, Jan. 27-28, 1978 (Box 64)
  - Executive Committee, 1978-03-16 (Box 64)
  - Board, Mar. 17-18, 1978 (Box 64)
  - Executive Committee, 1978-04-11 (Box 64)
  - Executive Committee, 9 May, 1978 (Box 64)
  - Executive Committee, 1978-05-27 (Box 64)
  - Board, May 28, 1978 (#1) (Box 65)
  - Board, May 28, 1978 (#2) (Box 65)
  - Executive Committee, 1978-07-18 (Box 65)
  - Executive Committee, 1978-09-12 (Box 65)
  - Executive Committee, 1978-10-19 (Box 65)
  - Board, Oct. 20-21, 1978 (Box 65)
  - Executive Committee, 1978-11-14 (Box 65)
  - Executive Committee, 1978-12-12 (Box 65)
  - Executive Committee, 1979-01-18 (Box 65)
  - Board, Jan. 19-20, 1979 (Box 65)
  - Executive Committee, 1979-03-15 (Box 65)
  - Board, Mar. 16-17, 1979 (Box 66)
  - Executive Committee, 1 May, 1979 (Box 66)
  - Executive Committee, 1979-05-27 (Box 66)
  - Board, 1979-05-28 (Box 66)
  - Executive Committee, 1979-07-17 (Box 66)
  - Executive Committee, 1979-09-11 (Box 66)
  - Executive Committee, 1979-10-11 (Box 66)
  - Board, Oct. 12-13, 1979 (Box 66)
  - Executive Committee, 1979-11-13 (Box 66)
  - Trustee Orientation, 1979-12-10 (Box 66)
  - Executive Committee, 1979-12-10 (Box 66)
  - Executive Committee, 1980-01-24 (Box 67)
  - Board, Jan. 25-26, 1980 (Box 67)
  - Executive Committee, 1980-03-06 (Box 67)
  - Board, Mar. 7-8, 1980 (Box 67)
  - Executive Committee, 1980-04-29 (Box 67)
  - Executive Committee, 1980-05-25 (Box 67)
  - Board, 1980-05-26 (Box 67)
  - Executive Committee, 9 June, 1980 (Box 67)
  - Executive Committee, 8 July, 1980 (Box 67)
  - Trustee Orientation, 1980-09-9 (Box 67)
  - Executive Committee, 1980-09-9 (Box 67)
  - Board, Oct. 17-18, 1980 (Box 67)
  - Executive Committee, 1980-10-16 (Box 68)
  - Executive Committee, 1980-11-11 (Box 68)
  - Executive Committee, 1980-12-9 (Box 68)
  - Executive Committee, 1981-01-22 (Box 68)
  - Board of Trustees, Jan. 23-24, 1981 (Box 68)
  - Executive Committee, 1981-03-26 (Box 68)
  - Board of Trustees, Mar. 27-28, 1981 (Box 68)
  - Executive Committee, 1981-05-30 (Box 68)
  - Cornell Trustees/ SUNY Trustees, Apr. 28-29, 1982 (Box 68)
  - Executive Committee, 5 May, 1981 (Box 68)
  - Board of Trustees, 1981-05-30 (Box 68)
  - Executive Committee, 1981-07-14 (Box 69)
  - Orientation, Sept. 14-15, 1981 (Box 69)
  - Executive Committee, 1981-09-15 (Box 69)
  - Executive Committee, 1981-10-29 (Box 69)
  - Board of Trustees, Oct. 29-31, 1981 (Box 69)
  - Executive Committee, 1981-12-08 (Box 69)
  - Orientation, 1982-01-28 (Box 69)
  - Executive Committee, 1982-01-28 (Box 69)
  - Board of Trustees, Jan. 29-30, 1092 (Box 69)
  - Executive Committee, 1982-03-25 (Box 69)
  - Board of Trustees, 1982-03-26 (Box 69)
  - Executive Committee, 1982-04-27 (Box 69)
  - Board of Trustees, 1985-01 (Box 70)
  - Executive Committee, 1985-03 (Box 70)
  - Board of Trustees, 1985-03 (Box 70)
  - Executive Committee, 1985-04 (Box 70)
  - Board of Trustees, 1985-04 (Box 70)
  - Executive Committee, 1985-05 (Box 70)
  - Executive Committee, 1985-07 (Box 70)
  - Executive Committee, 1985-09 (Box 70)
  - Board of Trustees, 1985-10 (Box 70)
  - Executive Committee, 1985-12 (Box 70)
  - Board of Trustees, 1986-01 (Box 70)
  - Executive Committee, 1986-01 (Box 70)
  - Executive Committee, 1986-03 (Box 70)
  - Board of Trustees, 1986-03 (Box 70)
  - Board of Trustees, 1986-05 (Box 70)
  - Executive Committee, 1986-05 (Box 70)
  - Executive Committee, 1986-09 (Box 70)
  - Executive Committee, 1986-10 (Box 70)
  - Full Professor Write Ups (Chron. Copies) (Box 70)
  - Executive Committee, 1986-12 (Box 70)
  - Board of Trustees, 1986-10 (Box 70)
  - Executive Committee, 1987-01 (Box 71)
  - Board of Trustees, 1987-01 (Box 71)
  - Board of Trustees, 1987-03 (Box 71)
  - Executive Committee, 1987-04 (Box 71)
  - Board of Trustees, 1987-05 (Box 71)
  - Executive Committee, 1987-06 (Box 71)
  - Executive Committee, 1987-09 (Box 71)
  - Executive Committee, 1987-10 (Box 71)
  - Executive Committee, 1987-12 (Box 71)
  - Board of Trustees, 1988-01 (Box 71)
  - Board of Trustees, 1988-03 (Box 71)
  - Executive Committee, 1988-05 (Box 71)
  - Board of Trustees, 1988-05 (Box 71)
  - Executive Committee, July 88 (Box 71)
  - Executive Committee, 1988-09 (Box 71)
  - Executive Committee, 1988-10 (Box 71)
  - Board of Trustees, 1988-10 (Box 71)
  - Executive Committee, 1988-12 (Box 71)
  - Board of Trustees, 1989-01 (Box 72)
  - Board of Trustees/Exec. Comm., 1989-03 (Box 72)
  - Board of Trustees/Exec. Comm., 1989-05 (Box 72)
  - Executive Committee, 1989-06 (Box 72)
  - Executive Committee, 1989-09 (Box 72)
  - Board of Trustees/Exec. Comm., 1989-10 (Box 72)
  - Full Professor Promotions, 1990 (Box 72)
  - Board of Trustees/Exec. Comm., 1990-01 (Box 72)
  - Board of Trustees/Exec. Comm., 1990-03 (Box 72)
  - Board of Trustees/Exec. Comm., 1990-05 (Box 72)
  - Executive Committee, 1990-06 (Box 72)
  - Board of Trustees/Exec. Comm., 1990-09 (Box 72)
  - Executive Committee, 1990-12 (Box 72)
  - Full Professor Promotions, 1991 (Box 72)
  - Board of Trustees, 1991-01 (Box 72)
  - Board of Trustees/Exec. Comm., 1991-03 (Box 72)
  - Board of Trustees/Exec. Comm., 1991-05 (Box 72)
  - Executive Committee, 1991-06 (Box 72)
  - Executive Committee, 1991-09 (Box 72)
  - Executive Committee, 1982-05-29 (Box 73)
  - Board of Trustees, file I, 1982-05-29 (Box 73)
  - Board of Trustees, file II, 1982-05-29 (Box 73)
  - Executive Committee, 1982-07-13 (Box 73)
  - Orientation, Sept. 13-14, 1982 (Box 73)
  - Executive Committee, 1982-09-14 (Box 73)
  - Executive Committee, 1982-10-21 (Box 73)
  - Board of Trustees, Oct. 22-23, 1982 (Box 73)
  - Board of Trustees, Dec.'7, 1982 (Box 73)
  - Executive Committee, 1982-12-07 (Box 73)
  - Executive Committee, 1983-01-27 (Box 74)
  - Board of Trustees, Jan. 28-29, 1983 (Box 74)
  - Executive Committee, 1983-03-24 (Box 74)
  - Board of Trustees, Mar. 25-26, 1983 (Box 74)
  - Executive Committee, 1983-04-26 (Box 74)
  - Board of Trustees, 1983-04-26 (Box 74)
  - Executive Committee, 1983-05-28 (Box 74)
  - Board of Trustees, file I, 1983-05-28 (Box 74)
  - Board of Trustees, file II, 1983-05-28 (Box 74)
  - Executive Committee, 1983-07-12 (Box 74)
  - Executive Committee, 1983-09-13 (Box 74)
  - Orientation, 1983-10-06 (Box 75)
  - Board of Trustees, Oct. 7-8, 1983 (Box 75)
  - Executive Committee, 1983-12-06 (Box 75)
  - Board of Trustees, Jan. 27-28, 1984 (Box 75)
  - Executive Committee, 1984-02-18 (Box 75)
  - Executive Committee, 1984-03-22 (Box 75)
  - Board of Trustees, 1984-03-23 (Box 75)
  - Executive Committee, 1984-05-26 (Box 75)
  - Board of Trustees, 1984-05-26 (Box 75)
  - Executive Committee, 1984-07-10 (Box 76)
  - Executive Committee, 1984-07-23 (Box 76)
  - Orientation, 1984-09-11 (Box 76)
  - Executive Committee, 1984-09-11 (Box 76)
  - Executive Committee, 1984-10-18 (Box 76)
  - Board of Trustees, Oct. 19-20, 1984 (Box 76)
  - Special meeting, 1984-10-31 (Box 76)
  - Executive Committee, 1984-12-11 (Box 76)
  - Executive Committee, 1985-01-11 (Box 76)
  - Board of Trustees, Jan. 25-26, 1985 (Box 76)
  - Executive Committee, 1985-03-28 (Box 76)
  - Board of Trustees, Mar. 29-30, 1985 (Box 76)
  - Executive Committee, 1985-04-23 (Box 76)
  - Executive Committee, 1 June, 1985 (Box 76)
  - Board of Trustees, 1 June, 1985 (Box 76)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, Oct. 17, 1865 - June 1872 (Box 77)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, Oct. 1873 -June 1885 (Box 78)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1886-10-1898-06 (Box 79)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1899-10-1908-06 (Box 80)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1909-10-1911-06 (Box 81)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, Oct. 1912 -June 1913 (Box 82)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1914-10-1916-06 (Box 83)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, Oct. 1917 - 1920? (Box 84)
  - Executive Committee, 9 July, 1985 (Box 85)
  - Executive Committee, 1985-09 (Box 85)
  - Orientation, 1985-10-10 (Box 85)
  - Executive Committee, 1985-10-10 (Box 85)
  - Board of Trustees, Oct. 11- 12, 1985 (Box 85)
  - Executive Committee, 1985-10-24 (Box 85)
  - Executive Committee, 1985-12-05 (Box 85)
  - Executive Committee, 1986-01-30 (Box 85)
  - Board of Trustees, 1986-01-31 (Box 85)
  - Executive Committee, 1986-03-20 (Box 85)
  - Board of Trustees, 1986-03-21 (Box 85)
  - Executive Committee, 1986-05-19 (Box 85)
  - Executive Committee, 1986-05-31 (Box 85)
  - Board of Trustees, May 31 ,1986 (Box 86)
  - Orientation, 1986-06-26 (Box 86)
  - Executive Committee, 1986-06-26 (Box 86)
  - Executive Committee, 1986-09-04 (Box 86)
  - Executive Committee, 1986-10-16 (Box 86)
  - Board of Trustees, Oct. 17-18, 1986 (Box 86)
  - Executive Committee, 1986-12-04 (Box 86)
  - Executive Committee, 1986-12-19 (Box 86)
  - Executive Committee, 1987-01-29 (Box 86)
  - Board of Trustees, Jan. 30-3 1,1987 (Box 86)
  - Executive Committee, 1987-03-20 (Box 86)
  - Board of Trustees, Mar. 19-21, 1987 (Box 86)
  - Executive Committee, 1987-04-02 (Box 86)
  - Executive Committee, 1987-04-16 (Box 86)
  - Executive Committee, 1987-04-29 (Box 86)
  - Executive Committee, 1987-05-30 (Box 86)
  - Board of Trustees, 5/30/87 (Box 87)
  - Executive Committee, 1987-06-25 (Box 87)
  - Executive Committee, 1987-09-10 (Box 87)
  - Executive Committee, 1987-09-17 (Box 87)
  - Orientation, 1987-10-22 (Box 87)
  - Executive Committee, 1987-10-22 (Box 87)
  - Board of Trustees, Oct. 23-24, 1987 (Box 87)
  - Executive Committee, 1987-12-10 (Box 87)
  - Executive Committee, 1988-01-28 (Box 87)
  - Board of Trustees, Jan. 29-30, 1988 (Box 87)
  - Executive Committee, 1988-02-25 (Box 87)
  - Executive Committee, 1988-03-15 (Box 87)
  - Board of Trustees, 1988-03-16 (Box 88)
  - Executive Committee, 1988-04-20 (Box 88)
  - Executive Committee, 1988-05-28 (Box 88)
  - Board of Trustees, 5/28/88 (Box 88)
  - Executive Committee, 6 July, 1988 (Box 88)
  - Orientation, 6 July, 1988 (Box 88)
  - Executive Committee, 1988-09-08 (Box 88)
  - Executive Committee, 1988-09-28 (Box 88)
  - Executive Committee, 1988-10-13 (Box 88)
  - Board of Trustees, Oct. 14-15, 1988 (Box 88)
  - Executive Committee, 1988-11-29 (Box 88)
  - Executive Committee (w/DSS), 1988-12-08 (Box 88)
  - Executive Committee, 1988-12-08 (Box 88)
  - Executive Committee, 1989-01-26 (Box 88)
  - Board of Trustees, Jan. 27-28, 1989 (Box 89)
  - Executive Committee, 1989-02-10 (Box 89)
  - Executive Committee, 1989-02-18 (Box 89)
  - Executive Committee, 1989-03-16 (Box 89)
  - Board of Trustees, Mar. 17-18, 1989 (Box 89)
  - Executive Committee, 1989-04-19 (Box 89)
  - Executive Committee, 1989-05-27 (Box 89)
  - Board of Trustees, 1989-05-27 (Box 89)
  - Executive Committee, 1989-06-29 (Box 89)
  - Executive Committee, 1989-09-07 (Box 89)
  - Executive Committee (cancelled), 10/26/89 (Box 89)
  - Board, October 27-28, 1989 (Box 89)
  - Executive Committee, 11/27/89 (Box 89)
  - Executive Committee, 12/14/89 (Box 89)
  - Executive Committee, 1/20/94 (Box 90)
  - Board of Trustees, January 21-22, 1994 (Box 90)
  - Executive Committee, 3/17/94 (Box 90)
  - Board of Trustees, March 17-18, 1994 (Box 90)
  - Executive Committee, 4/21/94 (Box 90)
  - Executive Committee, 5/27/94 (Box 90)
  - Board of Trustees, 5/28/94 (Box 90)
  - Orientation, June 22-23, 1994 (Box 90)
  - Executive Committee, 6/23/94 (Box 90)
  - Executive Committee, 9/8/94 (Box 90)
  - Board of Trustees, October 21-22, 1994 (Box 90)
  - Executive Committee, 11/21/94 (Box 90)
  - Executive Committee, 12/8/94 (Box 90)
  - Board of Trustees, 12/10/94 (Box 90)
  - Executive Committee, 1/26/95 (Box 90)
  - Board of Trustees, 1/27/95 (Box 90)
  - Board of Trustees, 3/17/95 (Box 91)
  - Executive Committee, 4/20/95 (Box 91)
  - Executive Committee, 5/26/95 (Box 91)
  - Board of Trustees, 5/27/95 (Box 91)
  - Executive Committee, 6/27/95 (Box 91)
  - Orientation, 9/7/95 (Box 91)
  - Executive Committee, 9/7/95 (Box 91)
  - Board of Trustees, October 13-14, 1995 (Box 91)
  - Executive Committee, 11/20/95 (Box 91)
  - Executive Committee, 12/7/95 (Box 91)
  - Board of Trustees Proceedings, 2010-2011 (Box 91)
  - Executive Committee, 1996-01 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees, 1996-01 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee, 1996-03 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees, 3/29/96 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee, 1996-04 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees, 1996-05 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Subcommittee on Salaries, 1996-05 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee, 1996-05 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Orientation, 1996-06 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Executive Committee, 1996-06 (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - Executive Committee, 1996-09 (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - Executive Committee, 1996-09 (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - Board of Trustees, 1996-10 (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - Executive Committee, 1996-11 (Box 93, Folder 14)
  - Executive Committee, 1996-12 (Box 93, Folder 15)
  - Board of Trustees, 1997-01 (Box 93, Folder 16)
  - Board of Trustees, 1997-03 (Box 93, Folder 17)
  - Executive Committee, 1997-04 (Box 93, Folder 18)
  - Board of Trustees, 1997-05 (Box 93, Folder 19)
  - Orientation, 1997-06 (Box 93, Folder 20)
  - Executive Committee, 1997-06 (Box 93, Folder 21)
  - Executive Committee, 1997-09 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees, 1997-10 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee, 1997-12 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Executive Commmittee, 1997-12 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees, 1998-01 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees, 1998-03 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee, 1998-04 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee, 1998-04 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Executive Committee, 1998-05 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Board of Trustees, 1998-05 (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Executive Committee, 1998-06 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Executive Committee, 1998-09 (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Board of Trustees, 1998-10 (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Executive Committee, 1998-12 (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - Board of Trustees, 1999-01 (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - Board of Trustees, 1999-03 (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - Executive Committee, 1999-04 (Box 94, Folder 17)
  - Executive Committee, 1999-05 (Box 94, Folder 18)
  - Board of Trustees, 1999-05 (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - Orientation, 1999-06 (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - Executive Committee, 1999-06 (Box 94, Folder 21)
  - Ex Com, 9/9/99 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Board, 10/9/99 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Ex Com, 12/9/99 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Board, January 28-29, 2000 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Ex Com, 1/28/00 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Ex Com, 2/1/00 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Board, 3/10/00 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Ex Com, 4/20/00 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Ex Com, 5/26/00 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Board, 5/27/00 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - Orientation, June 21-22, 2000 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Ex Com, 6/22/00 (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - Ex Com, 9/7/00 (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - Board, October 27-28, 2000 (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - Ex Com, 10/27/00 (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - Ex Com, 12/7/00 (Box 95, Folder 16)
  - Board, January 26-27, 2001 (Box 95, Folder 17)
  - Ex Com, 1/16/01 (Box 95, Folder 18)
  - Board, 3/9/01 (Box 95, Folder 19)
  - Ex Com, 4/19/01 (Box 95, Folder 20)
  - Ex Com, 5/25/01 (Box 95, Folder 21)
  - Board, May 25-26, 2001 (Box 95, Folder 22)
  - Ex Com, 6/21/01 (Box 95, Folder 23)
- Series III. Photographs
  - Walker Cislery, Chairman (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - John Collyer, Chairman (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Arthur Dean, Chairman (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Mary Honor Donlon, Vice-Chairman (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Robert Purcel, Chairman (1968-1978) (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Ellis Robison and Neal Stamp (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Neal Stamp, 1976 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Cornell Presidents Perkins, Malott, Corson, Rhodes, & Rawlings, 1995 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Cornell Presidents Rhodes, Corson, Perkins, & Malott, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Board of Trustees, 1969 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Group Shots (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Untitled (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Malott, Perkins, Carson, Rhodes at a dinner in Willard Straight Hall to celebrate Dale Corson's 80th birthday, 1994 (Folder 1)
  - Aerial view of campus (Folder 1)
  - Oversize Photo of the Board of Trustees, 1959 (Folder 1)
  - Inauguration of Frank Rhodes as 9th President, 1977-11 (Folder 1)